[
    {
        "answer": "Is that enough?",
        "question": "Этого достаточно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "No, thank you",
        "question": "Нет, спасибо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I feel good",
        "question": "Я хорошо себя чувствую",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long are you going to stay?",
        "question": "Как долго ты собираешься пребывать?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "More than 200 miles",
        "question": "Больше чем 200 миль",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll have a glass of water please.",
        "question": "Стакан воды, будьте добры.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've already seen it.",
        "question": "Я уже это видел.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm sorry, we're sold out",
        "question": "Извиняюсь, мы все распродали",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I think it's very good",
        "question": "Я думаю, что очень хорошо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the address?",
        "question": "Какой адрес?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you sell medicine? (store)",
        "question": "Вы продаете лекарства?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have they met her yet?",
        "question": "Они её уже встречали?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When is the next bus to Philidalphia?",
        "question": "Когда следующий автобус в Филадельфию?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you translate this for me?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы перевести это для меня?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One way or round trip?",
        "question": "В один конец или в оба?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to the American Embassy?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до Американского посольства?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I have a glass of water please?",
        "question": "Можно стакан воды, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I need to practice my English",
        "question": "Мне надо попрактиковать свой английский",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Take a chance",
        "question": "Воспользуйся шансом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you need anything?",
        "question": "Тебе что-нибудь нужно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's up?",
        "question": "В чём дело?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I lost my watch",
        "question": "Я потерял свои часы",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you think you'll be back by 11:30?",
        "question": "Ты думаешь, ты придёшь обратно до 11:30?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have to wash my clothes.",
        "question": "Мне надо постирать свои вещи.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's August 25th.",
        "question": "Сегодня 25 августа.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which one is better?",
        "question": "Который лучше?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are they the same?",
        "question": "Они одинаковые?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's 17 dollars.",
        "question": "Это стоит 17 долларов.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do people usually do in the summer in Los Angeles?",
        "question": "Чем люди обычно занимаются летом в Лос Анжелесе?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know how to cook?",
        "question": "Ты умеешь готовить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a table near the window.",
        "question": "Я бы хотел столик около окна.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take by car?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает на машине?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There are some apples in the refrigerator.",
        "question": "Несколько яблок в холодильнике.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When does it arrive?",
        "question": "Когда ого прибудет?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My daughter is here.",
        "question": "Моя дочь здесь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have enough money?",
        "question": "У вас достаточно денег?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Okay",
        "question": "Хорошо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's too bad",
        "question": "Это очень плохо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm hungry",
        "question": "Я голоден",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Он любит сок, но ему не нравится молоко.",
        "question": "Он любит сок, но ему не нравится молоко.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What size?",
        "question": "Какой размер?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "No, this is the first time.",
        "question": "Нет, это первый раз.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I was going to the library",
        "question": "Я собирался в библиотеку",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What day of the week is it?",
        "question": "В какой день недели?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My grandmother passed away last year.",
        "question": "Мой бабушка скончалась в прошлом году.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Great",
        "question": "Превосходно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What does this say?",
        "question": "Что здесь сказано?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know her?",
        "question": "Ты её знаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "She's older than me.",
        "question": "Она старше меня.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a map of the city.",
        "question": "Мне нужна карта города.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll tell him you called.",
        "question": "Я скажу ему, что ты звонил.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll take that one also",
        "question": "Я возьму то тоже",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there anything cheaper?",
        "question": "Есть что-нибудь подешевле?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Maybe",
        "question": "Может быть",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm not busy",
        "question": "Я не занят",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long have you lived here?",
        "question": "Как долго ты жил здесь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How's business?",
        "question": "Как бизнес (работа)?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long will it take?",
        "question": "Сколько это займёт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That restaurant is not expensive",
        "question": "Ресторан недорогой",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you play basketball?",
        "question": "Ты играешь в баскетбол?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Not recently",
        "question": "Не недавно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "For how many nights?",
        "question": "На сколько ночей?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you feel better?",
        "question": "Ты чувствуешь себя лучше?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Were you at the library last night?",
        "question": "Ты был в библиотеке прошлой ночью?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there air conditioning in the room?",
        "question": "Есть ли в комнате кондиционер?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to Daniel Street?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до улицы Даниел?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I hope you and your wife have a nice trip",
        "question": "Я надеюсь, у тебя и твоей жены будет хорошая поездка",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Take this medicine.",
        "question": "Прими эти лекарства.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My son studies computers.",
        "question": "Мой сын изучает компьютеры.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "About 300 kilometers",
        "question": "Около 300 километров",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This is Mrs. Smith.",
        "question": "Это Миссис Смит.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is near the table",
        "question": "Книга около стола",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which school does he go to?",
        "question": "В какую школу он ходит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you swim?",
        "question": "Ты умеешь плавать?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you recommend?",
        "question": "Что вы порекомендуете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I understand.",
        "question": "Я понимаю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a single room",
        "question": "Мне нужен номер на одного человека",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where can I buy tickets?",
        "question": "Где я могу купить билеты?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a question.",
        "question": "I want to ask you.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please sit down.",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, садитесь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can it be cheaper?",
        "question": "Может это быть дешевле?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's in it?",
        "question": "Что там?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My name is John Smith.",
        "question": "Меня зовут Джон Смит.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's this?",
        "question": "Что это?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "From time to time",
        "question": "Время от времени",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you afraid?",
        "question": "Ты боишься?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your religion?",
        "question": "Какая у тебя религия?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I forget.",
        "question": "Я забыл.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do your parents do for work?",
        "question": "Чем занимаются ваши родители?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "She's pretty",
        "question": "Она симпотичная",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please call me",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, позвони мне",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a non-smoking room.",
        "question": "Я предпочитаю комнату для некурящих.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They'll be right back",
        "question": "Они скоро вернуться",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm very busy. I don't have time now",
        "question": "Я очень занят. У меня сейчас нет времени",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who are they?",
        "question": "Кто они?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I wish I had one",
        "question": "Хотел бы я иметь один такой",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My father has been there.",
        "question": "Мой отец был там.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One ticket to New York please",
        "question": "Один билет до Нью-Йорка, пожалуйста",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there a store near here?",
        "question": "Есть где-нибудь здесь магазин?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you recommend a good restaurant?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы порекомендовать хороший ресторан?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is she from?",
        "question": "Откуда она?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How was the movie?",
        "question": "Как был фильм?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My watch has been stolen.",
        "question": "Мои часы украдены.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How is she?",
        "question": "Как она?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you like it here?",
        "question": "Тебе здесь нравится?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Behind the bank.",
        "question": "Сзади банка.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is the bank far?",
        "question": "Далеко ли банк?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Какой у тебя электронный адрес?",
        "question": "Какой у тебя электронный адрес?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which one is the best?",
        "question": "Который самый лучший?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll take that one also",
        "question": "Я возьму то тоже",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to have dinner with me?",
        "question": "Не хотите поужинать со мной?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to call the United States.",
        "question": "Я хотел бы позвонить в Соединенные Штаты.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's is a quarter past nine",
        "question": "Сейчас четверть десятого",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Yes, really",
        "question": "Да, действительно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's practice English",
        "question": "Давайте попрактикуем английский",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like something to eat?",
        "question": "Не хотите что-нибудь поесть?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm looking for the post office",
        "question": "Я ищу почту",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 3 o'clock",
        "question": "В 3 часа",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where are you going to go?",
        "question": "Куда ты собираешься пойти?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The cars are American.",
        "question": "Машины американские.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm just kidding.",
        "question": "Я шучу.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which one is cheaper?",
        "question": "Который дешевле?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you allergic to anything?",
        "question": "У тебя есть аллергия на что-либо?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I still have a lot to do.",
        "question": "Мне ещё много чего нужно сделать.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the second floor",
        "question": "На втором этаже.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your favorite food?",
        "question": "Какая твоя любимая еда?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know where she is?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, где она?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a headache",
        "question": "У меня головная боль",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At what time?",
        "question": "Во сколько?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Near the bank",
        "question": "Около банка",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What would you like to drink?",
        "question": "Что бы ты хотел выпить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time do you think you'll arrive?",
        "question": "В какое время ты думаешь ты приедешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it possible?",
        "question": "Это возможно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want me to come and pick you up?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь, чтобы я заехал и захватил тебя?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long will you be staying?",
        "question": "Как долго вы будете находиться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to buy a phone card please.",
        "question": "Я бы хотел купить телефонную карточку, пожалуйста.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm ready.",
        "question": "Я готов.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where do you work?",
        "question": "Где ты работаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I have a receipt please?",
        "question": "Можно чек, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How about Saturday?",
        "question": "Как насчёт субботы?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There's plenty of time.",
        "question": "Много времени.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did you put it?",
        "question": "Куда ты это положил?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Когда ты поедешь домой постарайся ехать медленно",
        "question": "When you go home, try to drive slowly",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Across from the post office",
        "question": "Напротив почты",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Take me to the Marriott Hotel.",
        "question": "Отвезите меня в отель Мариотт.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm good.",
        "question": "Я хорошо.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I need to go home",
        "question": "Мне нужно идти домой",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It hurts here.",
        "question": "Здесь болит.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is the bank far?",
        "question": "Далеко ли банк?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm 26 years old",
        "question": "Мне 26 лет",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I like to watch TV",
        "question": "Я люблю смотреть телевизор",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I was about to leave the restaurant when my friends arrived",
        "question": "Я собирался покинуть ресторан, когда пришли мои друзья",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When do you get off work?",
        "question": "Когда ты освобождаешься с работы?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do you pronounce that?",
        "question": "Как ты это произносишь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you eaten at that restaurant?",
        "question": "Ты кушал в этом ресторане?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The whole day.",
        "question": "Весь день.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What is it?",
        "question": "Что это?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please fill out this form",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, заполните эту форму",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I haven't been there.",
        "question": "Я там не был.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What did you do last night?",
        "question": "Что ты делал прошлой ночью?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't speak very well",
        "question": "Я не очень хорошо разговариваю",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you comfortable?",
        "question": "Тебе удобно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are you leaving?",
        "question": "Когда ты уезжаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Everyday I get up at 6AM.",
        "question": "Каждый день я встаю в 6 утра.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's north of here.",
        "question": "Это на севере отсюда.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What kind of music do you like?",
        "question": "Какая музыка тебе нравится?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I think you have too many clothes",
        "question": "Я думаю, что у тебя очень много вещей.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the right",
        "question": "Направо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We're from California",
        "question": "Мы из Калифорнии",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who are you looking for?",
        "question": "Кого вы ищете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How old are you?",
        "question": "Сколько вам лет?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "A one way ticket",
        "question": "Билет в один конец",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My house is close to the bank",
        "question": "Мой дом близок к банку",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm from America.",
        "question": "Я из Америки.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 3 o'clock",
        "question": "В 3 часа",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you accept U.S. Dollars?",
        "question": "Вы принимаете американские доллары?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How tall are you?",
        "question": "Каков ваш рост?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's go have a look",
        "question": "Давайте пойдем, посмотрим",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time does the store open?",
        "question": "В какое время открывается магазин?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I still have a lot of things to buy.",
        "question": "Мне всё ещё нужно купить много вещей.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time are they arriving?",
        "question": "В какое время они приезжают?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I bought a shirt yesterday.",
        "question": "Я купил рубашку вчера.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What does your father do for work?",
        "question": "Чем занимается твой отец?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How far is it to Chicago?",
        "question": "Как это далеко до Чикаго?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't care.",
        "question": "Мне всё равно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I get off of work at 6",
        "question": "Я покинул рабочее место в 6",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm not sure",
        "question": "Я не уверен",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's alright",
        "question": "Все в порядке",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm full",
        "question": "Я сыт.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long is the flight?",
        "question": "Насколько долог полёт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How was the movie?",
        "question": "Как был фильм?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry, I didn't hear clearly.",
        "question": "Извините, я не расслышал.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Hello",
        "question": "Здравствуйте",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When will he be back?",
        "question": "Когда он вернется?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm a teacher.",
        "question": "Я учитель.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You have a very nice car.",
        "question": "У тебя очень хорошая машина.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I use your phone?",
        "question": "Могу я воспользоваться твоим телефоном?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is on top of the table",
        "question": "Книга на столе",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please write it down",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, запишите это",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's enough",
        "question": "Этого достаточно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My throat is sore.",
        "question": "Мое горло воспалено.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The food was delicious.",
        "question": "Еда была вкусной.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have a swimming pool?",
        "question": "У тебя есть плавательный бассейн?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good afternoon",
        "question": "Добрый день",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where do you want to go?",
        "question": "Куда ты хочешь пойти?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you think?",
        "question": "Что вы думаете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Am I pronouncing it correctly?",
        "question": "Я это правильно произношу?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Isn't it?",
        "question": "Не так ли?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take to get to Georgia?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает добраться до Джорджии?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They're the same",
        "question": "Они одинаковые",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's 8:45.",
        "question": "Сейчас 8:45.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm looking for the post office",
        "question": "Я ищу почту",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are you thinking about?",
        "question": "О чём ты думаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry, we don't have any vacancies.",
        "question": "Извините, у нас нет свободных мест.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Help!",
        "question": "Помогите!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you think it'll rain today?",
        "question": "Ты думаешь, сегодня пойдет дождь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want to come with me?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь пойти со мной?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's on 7th street",
        "question": "Это на 7-ой улице",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's go",
        "question": "Пошлите",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take by car?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает на машине?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm coming right now",
        "question": "Я сейчас приду",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's there.",
        "question": "Это там.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Over here",
        "question": "Вот здесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you going to attend their wedding?",
        "question": "Ты собираешься посетить их свадьбу?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which is better, the spaghetti or chicken salad?",
        "question": "Что лучше, спагетти или куриный салат?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want to go with me?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь пойти со мной?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good morning",
        "question": "Доброе утро",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you ask him to call me back please?",
        "question": "Ты не попросишь его перезвонить мне, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We'll have two glasses of water please.",
        "question": "Нам два стакана воды, пожалуйста.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you been to Boston?",
        "question": "Ты был в Бостоне?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm looking for the post office",
        "question": "Я ищу почту",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We like it very much",
        "question": "Нам это очень нравится",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take to get to Georgia?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает добраться до Джорджии?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "A long time ago",
        "question": "Давно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll take it",
        "question": "Я возьму это",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are you moving?",
        "question": "Когда вы переезжаете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's very cold today.",
        "question": "Сегодня очень холодно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I need to change clothes",
        "question": "Мне нужно сменить одежду",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Does it often snow in the winter in Massachusetts?",
        "question": "Часто зимой в Массачусетсе идет снег?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry, we only accept Cash",
        "question": "Извините, мы принимаем только наличными",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who's calling?",
        "question": "Кто звонит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How far is it?",
        "question": "Как это далеко?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "it's not suppose to rain today",
        "question": "Сегодня не обещали дождь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good Luck",
        "question": "Удачи",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry, we don't have any",
        "question": "К сожалению, у нас нет",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is in front of the table",
        "question": "Книга спереди стола",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm leaving Tomorrow",
        "question": "Я уезжаю завтра",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What does this mean?",
        "question": "Что это означает?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't like him",
        "question": "Он мне не нравится",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the temperature?",
        "question": "Какова температура?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the room rate?",
        "question": "Какова цена за комнату?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I want to ask you a question.",
        "question": "У меня есть к тебе вопрос",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll have the same thing",
        "question": "У меня будет то же самое",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There's a restaurant near here.",
        "question": "Ресторан расположен неподалеку.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thank you very much",
        "question": "Спасибо большое",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where can I mail this?",
        "question": "Где я могу это отправить по почте?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know how to cook?",
        "question": "Ты умеешь готовить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That car is similar to my car.",
        "question": "Машина похожа на мою машину.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there a restaurant in the hotel?",
        "question": "Есть ли ресторан в отеле?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At what time did it happen?",
        "question": "Во сколько это произошло?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is your son here?",
        "question": "Твой сын здесь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you speak English?",
        "question": "Вы говорите по-английски?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Chicago is very different from Boston",
        "question": "Чикаго очень отличается от Бостона",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you need anything else?",
        "question": "Тебе нужно еще что-нибудь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I help you?",
        "question": "Могу я вам помочь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a phone call",
        "question": "Я хотел бы сделать звонок",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm going to bed.",
        "question": "Я иду спать.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There are some books on the table",
        "question": "Несколько книг на столе",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Does this road go to New York?",
        "question": "Это дорога ведёт в Нью-Йорк?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you arrived?",
        "question": "Ты приехал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He works at a computer company in New York.",
        "question": "Он работает в компьютерной компании в Нью-Йорке.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know where she is?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, где она?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it cold outside?",
        "question": "На улице холодно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's less than 5 dollars",
        "question": "Это меньше, чем 5 долларов",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm leaving Tomorrow",
        "question": "Я уезжаю завтра",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you been to Boston?",
        "question": "Ты был в Бостоне?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you fix this?",
        "question": "Ты можешь это починить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know what this says?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, что тут сказано?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you hold this for me?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы подержать это за меня?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a question.",
        "question": "I want to ask you.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much will it cost?",
        "question": "Сколько это будет стоить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who taught you that?",
        "question": "Кто тебя этому научил?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is everything ok?",
        "question": "Все хорошо?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you seen this movie?",
        "question": "Ты видел этот фильм?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's really hot",
        "question": "Сейчас очень жарко",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm cold",
        "question": "Мне холодно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll come back later",
        "question": "Я приду назад позже",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Did you send me flowers?",
        "question": "Ты посылал мне цветы?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My father is a lawyer.",
        "question": "Мой отец - юрист.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What should I wear?",
        "question": "Что мне надеть?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have this in size 11?",
        "question": "У вас есть это 11-го размера?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know how to get to the Marriott Hotel?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, как добраться до отеля Мариотт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's longer than 2 miles",
        "question": "Это больше, чем 2 мили",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Near the bank",
        "question": "Около банка",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like some wine?",
        "question": "Не хотите немного вина?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Should I wait?",
        "question": "Мне надо подождать?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's suppose to rain tomorrow",
        "question": "На завтра обещали дождь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let me think about it",
        "question": "Позвольте мне подумать об этом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 5th street",
        "question": "На 5-ой улице.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to go home.",
        "question": "Я хотел бы поехать (пойти) домой.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thank you sir",
        "question": "Спасибо, сэр",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Hurry!",
        "question": "Поторопись!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get there?",
        "question": "Как мне туда добраться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's half past 11",
        "question": "Сейчас пол-двенадцатого",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time does the movie start?",
        "question": "В какое время начинается кино?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm coming to pick you up",
        "question": "Я иду захватить тебя",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One ticket to New York please",
        "question": "Один билет до Нью-Йорка, пожалуйста",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That looks great",
        "question": "Это выглядит превосходно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Why did you say that?",
        "question": "Почему ты это сказал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The plane departs at 5:30PM",
        "question": "Самолёт вылетает в 5:30 вечера",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "She wants to know when you're coming.",
        "question": "Она хочет знать, когда ты приходишь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There's a restaurant over there, but I don't think it's very good.",
        "question": "Вон там есть ресторан, но я не думаю, что он очень хороший.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know her?",
        "question": "Ты её знаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much are these earrings?",
        "question": "Почём эти серьги?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's not very expensive.",
        "question": "Это не очень дорого.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There are many people here",
        "question": "Здесь много людей",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you hear that?",
        "question": "Ты это слышишь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you please say that again?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы сказать это еще раз, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do you spell it?",
        "question": "Как ты произнесёшь по буквам?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They charge 26 dollars per day",
        "question": "Они берут 26 долларов в день",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is this pen yours?",
        "question": "Это твоя ручка?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Very good, thanks",
        "question": "Очень хорошо, спасибо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I can't hear you clearly.",
        "question": "Я не ясно тебя слышу.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where would you like to meet?",
        "question": "Где бы ты хотел встретиться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's suppose to rain tomorrow",
        "question": "На завтра обещали дождь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I like her",
        "question": "Она мне нравится",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I was in the library",
        "question": "Я был в библиотеке",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's very important.",
        "question": "Это очень важно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's on 7th street",
        "question": "Это на 7-ой улице",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This is my mother.",
        "question": "Это моя мама.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to eat at 5th street restaurant",
        "question": "Я хотел бы поесть в ресторане на 5-ой улице",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the left.",
        "question": "Налево.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is your house like this one?",
        "question": "Твой дом такой как этот?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There's a book under the table",
        "question": "Книга лежит под столом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where can I rent a car?",
        "question": "Где я могу взять в аренду машину?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm not afraid.",
        "question": "Я не боюсь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I give up.",
        "question": "Я сдаюсь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Follow me",
        "question": "Следуйте за мной",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I still haven't decided.",
        "question": "Я всё еще не решил.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Why are you laughing?",
        "question": "Почему вы смеетесь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long is the flight?",
        "question": "Насколько долог полёт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long have you been here?",
        "question": "Как долго ты был там?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "More than that",
        "question": "Больше чем это.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What happened?",
        "question": "Что случилось?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is he?",
        "question": "Где он?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where can I exchange U.S. dollars?",
        "question": "Где я могу обменять американские доллары?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Did you take your medicine?",
        "question": "Ты принял свои лекарства?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have another one?",
        "question": "У тебя есть еще один?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you call back later?",
        "question": "Ты можешь перезвонить попозже?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here it is",
        "question": "Вот.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm single",
        "question": "Я холост (незамужняя).",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is anyone else coming?",
        "question": "Кто-нибудь еще подойдет?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I can swim.",
        "question": "Я умею плавать.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get there?",
        "question": "Как мне туда добраться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a lot of things to do.",
        "question": "Мне надо сделать много вещей.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's very hard working.",
        "question": "Он очень трудолюбив.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I want to ask you a question.",
        "question": "У меня есть к тебе вопрос",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When does he arrive?",
        "question": "Когда он приезжает?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How was the trip?",
        "question": "Как была поездка?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you finished studying?",
        "question": "Ты закончил учиться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "See you tomorrow",
        "question": "До завтра",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much would you like?",
        "question": "Сколько вы хотите?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is there a doctor who speaks English?",
        "question": "Где доктор, который говорит по-английски?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did you learn English?",
        "question": "Где ты выучил английский язык?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you speak louder please?",
        "question": "Не мог бы ты говорить громче?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who was your teacher?",
        "question": "Кто был твоим учителем?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time are you going to the bus station?",
        "question": "В какое время ты идешь на автобусную остановку?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll take that one also",
        "question": "Я возьму то тоже",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It will arrive shortly.",
        "question": "Это прибудет скоро.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is that?",
        "question": "Сколько то стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It costs 20 dollars per hour.",
        "question": "Это стоит 20 долларов в час.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you take credit cards?",
        "question": "Вы принимаете кредитные карточки?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They're very busy",
        "question": "Они очень заняты",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it raining?",
        "question": "Идет дождь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long have you worked here?",
        "question": "Как долго ты здесь работал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where do you live?",
        "question": "Где ты живёшь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you ready?",
        "question": "Ты готов?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm going to leave",
        "question": "Я ухожу",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The roads are slippery.",
        "question": "Дороги скользкие.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have any coffee?",
        "question": "У тебя есть кофе?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time do you go to work everyday?",
        "question": "В какое время ты ходишь каждый день на работу?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "A little",
        "question": "Чуть-чуть",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm a size 8.",
        "question": "Мой размер 8.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did you work before you worked here?",
        "question": "Где ты работал прежде?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What is today's date?",
        "question": "Какая сегодня число?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The big one or the small one?",
        "question": "Маленький или большой?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You speak English very well.",
        "question": "Ты очень хорошо говоришь по-английски.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He likes it very much",
        "question": "Ему это очень нравится",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please take me to this address",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, довезите меня до этого адреса",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are they coming?",
        "question": "Когда они приезжают?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do you know?",
        "question": "Откуда ты знаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I speak two languages",
        "question": "Я говорю на двух языках.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you think it's going to rain tomorrow?",
        "question": "Ты думаешь, завтра пойдет дождь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I remember.",
        "question": "Я помню.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you going to help her?",
        "question": "Ты собираешься ей помочь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are you coming back?",
        "question": "Когда ты возвращаешься?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When I went to the store, they didn't have any apples.",
        "question": "Когда я пошел в магазин, у них не было яблок.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are you doing?",
        "question": "Что ты делаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here you are.",
        "question": "Вот, пожалуйста.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's go",
        "question": "Пошлите",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I bring my friend?",
        "question": "Можно мне привести свого друга/подругу?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The books are expensive",
        "question": "Книги дорогие.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm worried too.",
        "question": "Я тоже беспокоюсь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've been there.",
        "question": "Я был там.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do they study?",
        "question": "Что они изучают?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't like it",
        "question": "Мне это не нравится",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where are you?",
        "question": "Где ты?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Not yet",
        "question": "Еще нет",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many people are there in New York?",
        "question": "Сколько человек там в Нью-Йорке?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a phone call",
        "question": "Я хотел бы сделать звонок",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I wish I had one",
        "question": "Хотел бы я иметь один такой",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One way or round trip?",
        "question": "В один конец или в оба?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did it happen?",
        "question": "Где это произошло?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you study?",
        "question": "Что вы изучаете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to Daniel Street?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до улицы Даниел?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Turn right",
        "question": "Поверни направо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How's the weather?",
        "question": "Как погода?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't want it",
        "question": "Я не хочу это",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They arrived yesterday",
        "question": "...",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This is the first time I've been here.",
        "question": "Я здесь первый раз.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is it to go to Miami?",
        "question": "Сколько это будет стоить, чтобы доехать до Майами?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My birthday is August 27th.",
        "question": "Мой день рождения 27 августа.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm cleaning my room",
        "question": "Я навожу порядок в своей комнате",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's very annoying",
        "question": "Он очень раздражающий",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's in the kitchen",
        "question": "Он на кухне",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have any children?",
        "question": "У тебя есть дети?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Go straight ahead",
        "question": "Идите прямо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What does this word mean?",
        "question": "Что это слово обозначает?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your name?",
        "question": "Как тебя зовут?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I haven't finished eating.",
        "question": "Я не закончил кушать.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you do for work?",
        "question": "Чем вы занимаетесь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is an ATM?",
        "question": "Где банкомат?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is he from?",
        "question": "Откуда он?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where are you going?",
        "question": "Куда ты идешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you free tonight?",
        "question": "Ты свободен сегодня вечером?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm just looking. (Shopping)",
        "question": "Я просто просматриваю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One ticket to New York please",
        "question": "Один билет до Нью-Йорка, пожалуйста",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is this pen yours?",
        "question": "Это твоя ручка?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you sure?",
        "question": "Ты уверен?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long have you been in America?",
        "question": "Как долго ты был в Америке?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've seen it.",
        "question": "Я это видел.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's not fair",
        "question": "Это несправедливо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you ask him to come here?",
        "question": "Ты не попросишь его прийти сюда?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a room.",
        "question": "Мне нужна комната.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please speak slower",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, говорите медненнее",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's it",
        "question": "Вот и все",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I thought the clothes were cheaper",
        "question": "Я думал, что одежда была дешевле",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's raining.",
        "question": "Идет дождь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much money do you make?",
        "question": "Сколько денег ты делаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's wrong.",
        "question": "Это неправильно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Will you pass me the salt please?",
        "question": "Ты передашь мне соль, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Next time",
        "question": "В следующий раз",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "More than 200 miles",
        "question": "Больше чем 200 миль",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you married?",
        "question": "Ты замужем/женаты",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Be careful",
        "question": "Будь осторожен",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have an appointment?",
        "question": "У тебя назначена встреча?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He studies at Boston University",
        "question": "Он учится в Бостонском Университете",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you working Tomorrow?",
        "question": "Ты работаешь завтра?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Cheers!",
        "question": "Пока!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you busy?",
        "question": "Ты занят?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get there?",
        "question": "Как мне туда добраться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm not ready yet",
        "question": "Я еще не готов",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who sent this letter?",
        "question": "Кто отправил это письмо?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Everything is ready",
        "question": "Всё готово",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to have dinner with me?",
        "question": "Не хотите поужинать со мной?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's share.",
        "question": "Давайте поделимся.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there a movie theater nearby?",
        "question": "Есть где-нибудь поблизости кинотеатр?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you like your boss?",
        "question": "Тебе нравится твой босс?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "No, I'm American.",
        "question": "Нет, я американец.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That way",
        "question": "Туда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Take it outside",
        "question": "Вынеси это на улицу",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you waiting for someone?",
        "question": "Ты ждешь кого-то?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your favorite movie?",
        "question": "Какой твой любимый фильм?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When did this happen?",
        "question": "Когда это произошло?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many languages do you speak?",
        "question": "На скольких языках вы разговариваете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the left",
        "question": "Налево",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a reservation",
        "question": "У меня есть забронированное место",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which one do you want?",
        "question": "Который ты хочешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Try it",
        "question": "Попробуй это",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you smoke?",
        "question": "Вы курите?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did you learn it?",
        "question": "Где ты это выучил?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here it is",
        "question": "Вот",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a room with two beds please.",
        "question": "Мне нужна комната с двумя кроватями.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I speak a little English",
        "question": "Я говорю по-английски немного.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you want to do?",
        "question": "Чем вы хотите заняться?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How's work going?",
        "question": "Как идёт работа?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Really?",
        "question": "Действительно?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What did you do yesterday?",
        "question": "Что ты делал вчера?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "There has been a car accident.",
        "question": "Произошла автокатастрофа.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't understand",
        "question": "Я не понимаю",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like some water?",
        "question": "Не хотите воды?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have a girlfriend?",
        "question": "У тебя есть девушка?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to rent a movie?",
        "question": "Не хотите взять фильм напрокат?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is that?",
        "question": "Сколько то стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Certainly!",
        "question": "Конечно!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Right there",
        "question": "Прямо там",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Follow me",
        "question": "Следуйте за мной",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's half past 11",
        "question": "Сейчас пол-двенадцатого",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We're late.",
        "question": "Мы поздно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you arrived?",
        "question": "Ты приехал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm thirsty",
        "question": "У меня жажда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thank you miss",
        "question": "Спасибо, мисс",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I can't hear you",
        "question": "Я не слыщу тебя",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are your hobbies?",
        "question": "Какие у тебя хобби?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here you are",
        "question": "Вот, пожалуйста",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "All day",
        "question": "Весь день.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there any mail for me?",
        "question": "Есть ли для меня какая-нибудь почта?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a phone call",
        "question": "Я хотел бы сделать звонок",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll pay",
        "question": "Я заплачу",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't mind.",
        "question": "Я не против.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm married",
        "question": "Я замужем (женат)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Expiration date.",
        "question": "Срок годности.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have two sisters.",
        "question": "У меня две сестры.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When do you arrive in the U.S.?",
        "question": "Когда ты приезжаешь в США?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have a problem?",
        "question": "У тебя проблема?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a reservation",
        "question": "Я хотел бы забронировать место",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a cold.",
        "question": "У меня простуда.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm not married",
        "question": "Я не замужем (не женат)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please speak slower",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, говорите медненнее",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "John is going on vacation tomorrow.",
        "question": "Джон едет завтра на отдых.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you here alone?",
        "question": "Ты здесь один?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are you going to pick up your friend?",
        "question": "Когда ты собираешься забрать своего друга?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you go to Florida often?",
        "question": "Ты часто ездишь во Флориду?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know how much it costs?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, сколько это стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Does he like the school?",
        "question": "Ему нравится школа?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That means friend.",
        "question": "Это означает друг.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Turn around",
        "question": "Повернись кругом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Outside the hotel",
        "question": "Снаружи отеля",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your last name?",
        "question": "Какая у тебя фамилия?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a reservation",
        "question": "Я хотел бы забронировать место",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many hours a week do you work?",
        "question": "Сколько часов в неделю вы работаете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How are you playing?",
        "question": "Как ты играешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time did you wake up?",
        "question": "В какое время ты проснулся?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry, we don't accept credit cards",
        "question": "Извините, мы не принимаем кредитные карточки",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I trust you.",
        "question": "Я тебе доверяю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "May I speak to Mrs. Smith please?",
        "question": "Можно поговорить с Миссис Смит, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I borrow some money?",
        "question": "Можно мне одолжить немного денег?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the exchange rate for dollars?",
        "question": "Каков обменный курс долларов?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time does the movie start?",
        "question": "В какое время начинается кино?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it hot?",
        "question": "На улице жарко?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "See you later",
        "question": "До скорого",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He needs some new clothes.",
        "question": "Ему нужны новые вещи.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thank you",
        "question": "Спасибо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "If you need my help, please let me know",
        "question": "Если тебе нужна моя помощь, пожалуйста, дай мне знать",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are you two talking about?",
        "question": "О чём вы оба разговариваете?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time is it?",
        "question": "Сколько времени?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm going home in four days",
        "question": "Я еду домой через четыре дня",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many people do you have in your family",
        "question": "Сколько человек у вас в семье?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Will you remind me?",
        "question": "Ты напомнишь мне?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Try it (try this)",
        "question": "Примерь это.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time is check out?",
        "question": "В какое время нужно освободить номер?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to watch TV?",
        "question": "Не хотите посмотреть телевизор?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That smells bad",
        "question": "Это плохо пахнет",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Never mind",
        "question": "Ничего страшного",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You're very smart",
        "question": "Ты очень умный",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Happy Birthday",
        "question": "С днем рождения",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When will it be ready?",
        "question": "Когда это будет готово?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who's that man over there?",
        "question": "Кто тот мужчина вон там?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You're smarter than him",
        "question": "Ты умнее его.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll give you a call.",
        "question": "Я позвоню тебе.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have a pencil?",
        "question": "У теня есть карандаш?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the exchange rate?",
        "question": "Каков обменный курс?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Will you put this in the car for me?",
        "question": "Ты положешь это в машину за меня?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know where there's a store that sells towels?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, где магазин, который продает полотенца?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many miles is it to Pennsylvania?",
        "question": "Сколько миль отсюда до Пенсильвании?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who won?",
        "question": "Кто выиграл?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm self-employed.",
        "question": "Я работаю на себя.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is next to the table",
        "question": "Книга рядом со столом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Whose book is that?",
        "question": "Чья эта книга?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's too expensive",
        "question": "Это слишком дорого",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's right",
        "question": "Это правильно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I was in the library",
        "question": "Я был в библиотеке",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm fine, and you?",
        "question": "Я хорошо, а ты?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It depends on the weather.",
        "question": "Это зависит от погоды.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you study English?",
        "question": "Вы изучаете английский?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll have a cup of tea please.",
        "question": "Чашку чая, пожалуйста.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't have any money",
        "question": "У меня нет денег",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want me to come and pick you up?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь, чтобы я заехал и захватил тебя?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "6 dollars per hour.",
        "question": "6 долларов в час",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you play basketball?",
        "question": "Ты играешь в баскетбол?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I was going to the library",
        "question": "Я собирался в библиотеку",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Go straight ahead",
        "question": "Идите прямо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It rained very hard today.",
        "question": "Сегодня шел ливень.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't know how to use it",
        "question": "Я не знаю, как это использовать",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is it?",
        "question": "Сколько это стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's over there.",
        "question": "Это вон там.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who is it? (Inquiring about who is on the phone)",
        "question": "Кто это? (по телефону)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to buy this?",
        "question": "Не хотите купить это?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good idea",
        "question": "Хорошая идея",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "If you like it I can buy more.",
        "question": "Если тебе это нравится, я могу купить больше.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The plane departs at 5:30PM",
        "question": "Самолёт вылетает в 5:30 вечера",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I believe you.",
        "question": "Я вам верю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much do I owe you?",
        "question": "Сколько я вас должен?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Your children are very well behaved.",
        "question": "Ваши дети очень хорошо воспитаны.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Call me",
        "question": "Позвони мне.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When do you arrive?",
        "question": "Когда ты приезжаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "From here to there",
        "question": "От сюда до туда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like coffee or tea?",
        "question": "Не хотите ли кофе или чай?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Who was your teacher?",
        "question": "Кто был твоим учителем?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Has your brother been to California?",
        "question": "Твой брат был в Калифорнии?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's very famous",
        "question": "Он очень знаменит",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I got in an accident.",
        "question": "Я попал в аварию.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sometimes I go to sleep at 11PM, sometimes at 11:30PM.",
        "question": "Иногда я иду спать в 11 вечера, иногда - в 11:30.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I have the bill please?",
        "question": "Можно счёт, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How was the movie?",
        "question": "Как был фильм?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I want to ask you a question.",
        "question": "У меня есть к тебе вопрос",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Did your wife like California?",
        "question": "Твоей жене понравилась Калифорния?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I understand now.",
        "question": "Я теперь понимаю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 7 o'clock in the morning",
        "question": "В 7 часов утра.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I like to watch TV",
        "question": "Я люблю смотреть телевизор",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where's the post office?",
        "question": "Где почта?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to Daniel Street?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до улицы Даниел?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Did it snow yesterday?",
        "question": "Вчера шел снег?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We have two boys and one girl",
        "question": "У нас два мальчика и одна девочка.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I love you",
        "question": "Я люблю тебя",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are you going to do tonight?",
        "question": "Что ты собираешься делать сегодня вечером?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you sell batteries?",
        "question": "Вы продаете батарейки?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can we have a menu please.",
        "question": "Можно нам меню, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This is very difficult",
        "question": "Это очень тяжело",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you working today?",
        "question": "Ты работаешь сегодня?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to go shopping.",
        "question": "Я хотел бы сделать покупки.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much does it cost per day?",
        "question": "Сколько это стоит в день?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's going to snow today.",
        "question": "Сегодня будет снег.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When do you leave?",
        "question": "Когда ты уезжаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's 11:30pm",
        "question": "Сейчас 11:30 вечера",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's your favorite food?",
        "question": "Какая твоя любимая еда?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Нет",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Tell me",
        "question": "Скажи мне",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I only want a snack",
        "question": "Я хочу только лёгкую закуску",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll pay for the tickets",
        "question": "Я заплачу за билеты",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it ready?",
        "question": "Это готово?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have one in my car.",
        "question": "У меня есть один в машине.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I use your phone?",
        "question": "Могу я воспользоваться твоим телефоном?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "A few",
        "question": "Несколько",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let's meet in front of the hotel.",
        "question": "Давайте встретимся перед отелем.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time did you get up?",
        "question": "В какое время ты встал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you repeat that please?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы повторить это, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm going home in four days",
        "question": "Я еду домой через четыре дня",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long are you going to stay in California?",
        "question": "Как долго ты собираешься быть в Калифорнии?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 3 o'clock in the afternoon",
        "question": "В 3 часа дня.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you okay?",
        "question": "Ты в порядке?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here's your order.",
        "question": "Вот ваш заказ.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What does he do for work?",
        "question": "Чем он занимается?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm 32.",
        "question": "Мне 32.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't have enough money.",
        "question": "У меня не достаточно денег.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you arrived?",
        "question": "Ты приехал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He said you like to watch movies.",
        "question": "Он сказал, что ты любишь смотреть кино.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Nothing else",
        "question": "Больше ничего",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Let me check",
        "question": "Позвольте мне проверить",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please take me to the airport",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, довезите меня до аэропорта",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I think it tastes good",
        "question": "Я думаю, это очень вкусно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Don't do that.",
        "question": "Не делай это.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Be careful driving",
        "question": "Будь осторожен за рулем",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I usually drink coffee at breakfast",
        "question": "Я обычно на завтрак пью кофе.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That way",
        "question": "Туда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "She's an expert.",
        "question": "Она эксперт.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This doesn't work",
        "question": "Это не работает",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you want to buy?",
        "question": "Что вы хотите купить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "This is very important",
        "question": "Это очень важно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know what this says?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, что тут сказано?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I made this cake.",
        "question": "Я приготовил этот пирог.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have the number for a taxi?",
        "question": "У тебя есть номер такси?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Your daughter.",
        "question": "Ваша дочь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I need a doctor.",
        "question": "Мне нужен доктор.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's here.",
        "question": "Это здесь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where are the t-shirts?",
        "question": "Где футболки?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Why aren't you going?",
        "question": "Почему ты не идешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Over there",
        "question": "Вот там",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Why did you do that?",
        "question": "Почему ты это сделал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When does the bus leave?",
        "question": "Когда отъезжает автобус?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do people usually do in the summer in Los Angeles?",
        "question": "Чем люди обычно занимаются летом в Лос Анжелесе?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is that ok?",
        "question": "Это нормально?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm good, and you?",
        "question": "Я хорошо, а ты?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Did you get my email?",
        "question": "Ты получил мое электронное письмо?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do you say it in English?",
        "question": "Как ты скажешь по-английски?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please take me to the airport",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, довезите меня до аэропорта",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Nonsense",
        "question": "Абсурд",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Business is good.",
        "question": "Бизнес - это хорошо.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It'll be cold this evening.",
        "question": "Сегодня вечером будет холодно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've never seen that before",
        "question": "Я никогда этого раньше не видел",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thanks for your help",
        "question": "Спасибо за вашу помощь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's in the kitchen",
        "question": "Он на кухне",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How far is it to Chicago?",
        "question": "Как это далеко до Чикаго?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want me to come and pick you up?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь, чтобы я заехал и захватил тебя?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Go straight ahead",
        "question": "Идите прямо",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's too many",
        "question": "Это очень много",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Our children are in America.",
        "question": "Наши дети в Америке.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you give me an example?",
        "question": "Ты можешь привести пример?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm allergic to seafood.",
        "question": "У меня аллергия на морскую пищу.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't have a girlfriend",
        "question": "У меня нет девушки",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm a beginner.",
        "question": "Я начинающий.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I think I need to see a doctor.",
        "question": "Мне кажется мне надо увидеться с доктором.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He needs some new clothes.",
        "question": "Ему нужны новые вещи.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Excuse me, what did you say?",
        "question": "Извините, что Вы сказали?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They arrived yesterday",
        "question": "Они приехали вчера.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Anything else?",
        "question": "Что-нибудь еще?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "In 30 minutes.",
        "question": "Через 30 минут.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When does the plane arrive?",
        "question": "Когда прилетает самолет?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you sick?",
        "question": "Ты болен?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Fill it up, please. (gas station)",
        "question": "Наполните, пожалуйста. (на автозаправке)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know where I can get a taxi?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, где я могу вызвать такси?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "We can eat Italian or Chinese food.",
        "question": "Мы может есть итальянскую или китайскую еду.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do you spell the word \"Seattle?",
        "question": "Как ты произнесёшь по буквам слово \"Сиэттл\"?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have anything cheaper?",
        "question": "У вас есть что-нибудь подешевле?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Why not?",
        "question": "Почему бы и нет?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's coming soon",
        "question": "Он скоро приезжает (приходит)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "His family is coming tomorrow.",
        "question": "Его семья приезжает завтра.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where's the nearest hospital?",
        "question": "Где наиближайшая больница?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What are you going to order? (to have?)",
        "question": "Что ты собираешься заказать?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Over here",
        "question": "Вот здесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where did you go?",
        "question": "Куда ты пошел?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm leaving Tomorrow",
        "question": "Я уезжаю завтра",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Good evening sir",
        "question": "Добрый вечер, сэр",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much money do you have?",
        "question": "Сколько у тебя денег?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you coming this evening?",
        "question": "Ты приходишь этим вечером?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "A round trip ticket",
        "question": "Билет в два конца",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Turn left",
        "question": "Поверни налево",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Give me the pen.",
        "question": "Дай мне ручку.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many children do you have?",
        "question": "Сколько у вас детей?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "June 3rd.",
        "question": "3 июня.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's right",
        "question": "Он прав",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please come in",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, входите",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What do you have?",
        "question": "Что у вас есть?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When does the bank open?",
        "question": "Когда открывается банк?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have any money?",
        "question": "У тебя есть деньги?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I like it.",
        "question": "Мне это нравится.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is your husband also from Boston?",
        "question": "Твой муж тоже с Бостона?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many people in the restaurant?",
        "question": "Сколько человек в ресторане?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Excuse me.",
        "question": "Извините.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "See you tonight",
        "question": "Увидемся сегодня вечером",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like a single room",
        "question": "Мне нужен номер на одного человека",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Waiter!",
        "question": "Официант!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Try to say it.",
        "question": "Попробуй сказать это.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's going to be hot today (It will be hot today)",
        "question": "Сегодня будет жарко.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Everyone knows it",
        "question": "Все знают это",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is the airport?",
        "question": "Где аэропорт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there a movie theater nearby?",
        "question": "Есть где-нибудь поблизости кинотеатр?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's near the Supermarket",
        "question": "Это около супермаркета",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's a quarter to 7.",
        "question": "Сейчас без четверти 7.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Across from the post office",
        "question": "Напротив почты",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When are your birthday?",
        "question": "Когда твой день рождения?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Call the police",
        "question": "Позвони в полицию",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I only have 5 dollars.",
        "question": "У меня всего 5 долларов.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Be quiet",
        "question": "Будь тихим",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm getting ready to go out.",
        "question": "Я готов на выход.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't want that",
        "question": "Я не хочу то",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Follow me",
        "question": "Следуйте за мной",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I make an appointment for next Wednesday?",
        "question": "Могу я назначить встречу на следующую среду?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I believe you.",
        "question": "Я вам верю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you been waiting long?",
        "question": "Ты долго ждал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you like to watch TV?",
        "question": "Ты любишь смотреть телевизор?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you do me a favor?",
        "question": "Могу я попросить тебя об услуге?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you believe that?",
        "question": "Ты этому веришь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have a good trip",
        "question": "Хорошей поездки",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't think so.",
        "question": "Я так не думаю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Give me a call.",
        "question": "Позвони мне.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I know",
        "question": "Я знаю",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When was the last time you talked to your mother?",
        "question": "Когда ты разговаривал со своей мамой в последний раз?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm American.",
        "question": "Я американец.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How far is it?",
        "question": "Как это далеко?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to go for a walk",
        "question": "Я хотел бы прогуляться (пройтись пешком)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've heard Texas is a beautiful place",
        "question": "Я слышал, что Техас - красивое место",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Excellent",
        "question": "Отлично",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you show me?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы показать мне?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is under the table",
        "question": "Книга под столом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You're beautiful",
        "question": "Ты красивый",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know where my glasses are?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, где мои очки?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where's the mail box?",
        "question": "Где почтовый ящик?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you been to Boston?",
        "question": "Ты был в Бостоне?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What kind of music do you like?",
        "question": "Какая музыка тебе нравится?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you recommend a good restaurant?",
        "question": "Ты не мог бы порекомендовать хороший ресторан?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are they coming this evening?",
        "question": "Они приезжают (приходят) этим вечером?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where does it hurt?",
        "question": "Где болит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I thought he said something else.",
        "question": "Я думал, он сказал что-то ещё.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm going home in four days",
        "question": "Я еду домой через четыре дня",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My house is close to the bank",
        "question": "Мой дом близок к банку",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What is that?",
        "question": "Что то?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Were there any problems?",
        "question": "Там были проблемы?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "At 7 o'clock at night. (evening)?",
        "question": "В 7 часов вечера.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long is the flight?",
        "question": "Насколько долог полёт?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's delicious!",
        "question": "Это вкусно!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'd like to make a reservation",
        "question": "Я хотел бы забронировать место",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's really hot",
        "question": "Сейчас очень жарко",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you play any sports?",
        "question": "Ты играешь в какой-нибудь вид спорта?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much altogether?",
        "question": "Сколько итого?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Turn around",
        "question": "Повернись кругом",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I've been here for two days",
        "question": "Я здесь 2 дня.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's too late.",
        "question": "Слишком поздно.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please speak more slowly.",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, говорите немного медленней.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you help me?",
        "question": "Ты можешь мне помочь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How does it taste?",
        "question": "Как это на вкус?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The book is behind the table",
        "question": "Книга сзади стола",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Don't worry",
        "question": "Не беспокойтесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He'll be back in 20 minutes.",
        "question": "Он вернётся назад через 20 минут.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Does anyone here speak English?",
        "question": "Кто-нибудь здесь говорит по-английски?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please take me to the airport",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, довезите меня до аэропорта",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you American?",
        "question": "Ты американец?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm coming right now",
        "question": "Я сейчас приду",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I wish I had one",
        "question": "Хотел бы я иметь один такой",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What will the weather be like tomorrow?",
        "question": "Какая погода будет завтра?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Every week.",
        "question": "Каждую неделю.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I ate already",
        "question": "Я уже поел",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "October 22nd",
        "question": "22 октября.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What did you think?",
        "question": "Что ты думаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long is it?",
        "question": "Как долго?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know how to cook?",
        "question": "Ты умеешь готовить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Be quiet",
        "question": "Будь тихим",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Outside the hotel",
        "question": "Снаружи отеля.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Just a moment",
        "question": "Один момент",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you understand?",
        "question": "Ты понимаешь?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to go for a walk?",
        "question": "Не хотите пройтись?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where were you?",
        "question": "Где ты был?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll pay for dinner",
        "question": "Я заплачу на обед",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Forget it.",
        "question": "Забудьте это.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm coming right now",
        "question": "Я сейчас приду",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please speak slower",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, говорите медненнее",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's ok",
        "question": "Все нормально",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Of course",
        "question": "Конечно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know what this says?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, что тут сказано?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is Mr. Smith an American?",
        "question": "Мистер Смит американец?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Thanks for everything",
        "question": "Спасибо за все",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it close?",
        "question": "Это близко?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the second floor",
        "question": "На втором этаже",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Fill it up, please. (gas station)",
        "question": "Наполните, пожалуйста. (на автозаправке)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you like the book?",
        "question": "Тебе нравится книга?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm here on business.",
        "question": "Я здесь по делам.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you hungry?",
        "question": "Ты голоден?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is it?",
        "question": "Где это?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you have the number for a taxi?",
        "question": "У тебя есть номер такси?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I agree",
        "question": "Я согласен.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What day are they coming over?",
        "question": "В какой день они приезжают?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's not right",
        "question": "Это неправильно",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take by car?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает на машине?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where are you from?",
        "question": "Ты откуда?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Please speak English.",
        "question": "Пожалуйста, говорите на английском.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the charge per night? (Hotel)",
        "question": "Какова плата за ночь? (в отеле)",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's fine",
        "question": "Это нормально",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You're very nice",
        "question": "Ты очень милый",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "One way or round trip?",
        "question": "В один конец или в оба?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm sorry.",
        "question": "Я извиняюсь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Sorry to bother you",
        "question": "Извини, что помешал тебе",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to the American Embassy?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до Американского посольства?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you done this before?",
        "question": "Ты делал это раньше?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Bring me my shirt please.",
        "question": "Принеси мне, пожалуйста, мою рубашку.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What school did you go to?",
        "question": "В какую школу ты ходил?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many miles is it to Pennsylvania?",
        "question": "Сколько миль отсюда до Пенсильвании?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't speak English very well.",
        "question": "Я не очень хорошо разговариваю по-английски.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Waitress!",
        "question": "Официантка!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much does this cost?",
        "question": "Сколько это стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the matter?",
        "question": "В чём дело?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My stomach hurts.",
        "question": "Мой живот болит.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you eaten yet?",
        "question": "Ты уже кушал?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Your things are all here",
        "question": "Все твои вещи здесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is this?",
        "question": "Сколько это стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where is the bathroom?",
        "question": "Где ванная комната?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can you carry this for me?",
        "question": "Ты можешь понести это за меня?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How do I get to the American Embassy?",
        "question": "Как мне добраться до Американского посольства?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm happy",
        "question": "Я счастлив",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have a question.",
        "question": "I want to ask you.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Come here.",
        "question": "Подойди сюда.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Stop!",
        "question": "Остановитесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's not too far",
        "question": "Это не так далеко.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are there any concerts?",
        "question": "Есть ли какие-нибудь концерты?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "That's too much",
        "question": "Это очень много",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Right here",
        "question": "Прямо здесь",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time did you go to sleep?",
        "question": "В какое время ты пошел спать?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "On the right",
        "question": "Направо.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "From here to there",
        "question": "От сюда до туда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "My luggage is missing.",
        "question": "Мой багаж отсутствует.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "They arrived yesterday",
        "question": "Они приехали вчера",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are you going to take a plane or train?",
        "question": "Ты собираешься полететь на самолете или поехать на поезде?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What's the phone number?",
        "question": "Каков номер телефона?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can I have a glass of water please?",
        "question": "Можно стакан воды, пожалуйста?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't understand what your saying.",
        "question": "Я не понимаю, что ты говоришь.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How long does it take to get to Georgia?",
        "question": "Сколько это занимает добраться до Джорджии?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What would you like to eat?",
        "question": "Что бы ты хотел поесть?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "When did you arrive in Boston?",
        "question": "Когда ты приехал в Бостон?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you like your co-workers?",
        "question": "Тебе нравяться твои коллеги?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Have you ever had Potato soup?",
        "question": "Ты когда-нибудь пробовал картофельный суп?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Nice to meet you",
        "question": "Приятно с тобой познакомиться",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He's an Engineer.",
        "question": "Он инженер.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is it far from here?",
        "question": "Это далеко отсюда?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Where would you like to go?",
        "question": "Куда бы ты хотел пойти?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "He studies at Boston University",
        "question": "Он учится в Бостонском Университете",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Now or later?",
        "question": "Сейчас или позже?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Can we have some more bread please?",
        "question": "Можно нам побольше хлеба?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm an American",
        "question": "Я американец",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you know what this means?",
        "question": "Ты знаешь, что это означает?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is this pen yours?",
        "question": "Это твоя ручка?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How are you?",
        "question": "Как твои дела?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The plane departs at 5:30PM",
        "question": "Самолёт вылетает в 5:30 вечера",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Which one?",
        "question": "Который?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'm sick.",
        "question": "Я болен.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like to rent a movie?",
        "question": "Не хотите взять фильм напрокат?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Here is your salad.",
        "question": "Вот ваш салат.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll call you when I leave",
        "question": "Я позвоню тебе, когда буду уезжать",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like something to drink?",
        "question": "Не хотите что-нибудь выпить?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's 6AM.",
        "question": "Сейчас 6 утра.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "As soon as possible",
        "question": "Как можно скорее.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Are your children with you?",
        "question": "Твои дети с тобой?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How much is this?",
        "question": "Сколько это стоит?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you like a glass of water?",
        "question": "Не хотите ли стакан воды?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "How many?",
        "question": "Сколько?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Just a little",
        "question": "Немного",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's delicious!",
        "question": "Это вкусно!",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't feel well.",
        "question": "Я неважно себя чувствую.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Is there a nightclub in town?",
        "question": "Есть ли в городе ночной клуб?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I'll take you to the bus stop",
        "question": "Я довезу тебя до автобусной остановки",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's more than 5 dollars",
        "question": "Это больше, чем 5 долларов",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I have pain in my arm.",
        "question": "У меня болит рука.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Would you take a message please?",
        "question": "Не могли бы вы получить сообщение?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "I don't want to bother you",
        "question": "Я не хочу тебя беспокоить",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "It's far from here.",
        "question": "Это далеко отсюда.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "Do you want to go to the movies?",
        "question": "Ты хочешь пойти в кино?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "The accident happened at the intersection.",
        "question": "Авария произошла на перекрёстке.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "You look like my sister.",
        "question": "Ты выглядишь как моя сестра.",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "What time does it start?",
        "question": "В какое время это начинается?",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    },
    {
        "answer": "From here to there",
        "question": "От сюда до туда",
        "explanation": "",
        "source": "English phrases",
        "is_ready_to_add": false,
        "created": false,
        "examples": []
    }
]